gaggleamp.com 2016-05-06

# Privacy Policy | GaggleAMP

Go Back

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason. It is the responsibility of all users of GaggleAMP.com to revisit this page to check for changes. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully before accessing or using the Website. By accessing or using any part of the Website, you agree to become bound by the terms and conditions of this Agreement. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, then you may not access the Website or use any services.

By using GaggleAMP.com you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. “Processing” means using cookies on a computer or using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining, and disclosing information, all of which activities will take place in the United States. If you reside outside the U.S., your personally identifiable information will be transferred to the U.S., and processed and stored there under U.S. privacy standards. By visiting our Site and providing information to us, you consent to such transfer to, and processing in, the U.S.

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or our use of your personally identifiable information, please contact us at privacy@gaggleamp.com.

### Information Collection and Use

**Information Collected Upon Registration and Adding Social Media Accounts.** A Gaggle Members is required to become a registered user, and to submit certain personally identifiable information to GaggleAMP.com. This happens in a number of instances, such as when you sign up for the Service, share a message, and other present and future site interactions. Personally identifiable information that we may collect in such instances may include your IP address, full user name, password, email address, city, time zone, and other information that you decide to provide us with, or information that you allow us to collect at the time of adding a social media account.

**Use of Contact Information.**

In addition, we may use your contact information to market to you, and provide you with information about, our products and services, including but not limited to services on GaggleAMP.com. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such information or communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications or in your Manager or Member dashboard.

**Log Data.**

When you visit the Site, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website (“Log Data” ). This Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type or the domain from which you are visiting, the messages you share, the messages you decline, and any reward communication made with the Gaggle Manager. For most users accessing the Internet from an Internet service provider, your IP address will be different every time you log on. We use Log Data to monitor the use of the Site and of our Service, and for the Site’s technical administration. We do not associate your IP address with any other personally identifiable information to identify you personally, except as required to enforce this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use for the Website, or as necessary to protect the rights, property, or safety of GaggleAMP, its employees, customers, or other users.

**Aggregate Information Accessible by Gaggle Manager.**

Certain information is used in the aggregate to provide analytics to the Gaggle Manager. This information is not tied to you personally, but may contain demographic information about the Members of the Gaggle in part or as a whole. This aggregated information is also made available outside the Gaggle in order to provide overall site demographic information. This aggregate and non-personally identifiable information may be used by GaggleAMP and shared with or sold to third-parties.

**Personal Information Accessible by Gaggle Manager.**

By becoming a GaggleAMP Member, you authorize your personal information in the form of your name, friend and follower count (where applicable, but not user names or other personal information) and contact information (in the form of your email address) to be made available to the Gaggle Manager in part to facilitate Reward delivery and communication.

**Cookies.**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a user’s computer and the user’s browser provides to the website each time the user returns. GaggleAMP uses cookies to help GaggleAMP identify and track users, their usage of the GaggleAMP Website, and their website access preferences. GaggleAMP visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using GaggleAMP’s website, with the drawback that certain features of GaggleAMP’s Website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Do Not Track:**

Do Not Track (“DNT”) is a privacy preference that users can set in certain web browsers. DNT is a way for users to inform websites and services that they do not want certain information about their webpage visits collected over time and across websites or online services. GaggleAMP does not recognize or respond to browser-initiated DNT signals, as the Internet industry is currently still working toward defining exactly what DNT means, what it means to comply with DNT, and a common approach to responding to DNT.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure.**

Service Providers. We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us, including, without limitation, hosting and maintenance, customer relationship, database storage and management, and direct marketing campaigns. We will share your personally identifiable information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to binding contractual obligations requiring such third parties to maintain the privacy and security of your data.

**Business Transfers.**

GaggleAMP may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your personally identifiable information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, or in the event of bankruptcy. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if the new entity’s planned processing of your information differs materially from the terms set forth in this Privacy Policy.

**Security.**

GaggleAMP believes in the privacy of our website users. We safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information. We employ administrative, physical, and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. We will make any legally-required disclosures of any breach of security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically-stored personal data to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

**Payment.**

Our shopping cart is powered by Recurly Inc. based in San Francisco, CA. The company’s ecommerce platform is PCI-compliant, adhering to standards and protocols for building and maintaining secure networks for financial transactions. For more information on Recurly’s security policies click here.  
We use PayPal Pro as our merchant gateway to process all credit card transactions. You do not need your own Paypal account to purchase from our online store. Through Paypal we accept Mastercard, Visa, American Express, and Discover. Located in San Jose, California, Paypal was founded in 1998 and acquired by eBay in 2002. PayPal has its own privacy policy regarding how they collect and use your information and what you can do to restrict that. Review their privacy statement here: https://cms.paypal.com/cgi-bin/marketingweb?cmd= _render-content &content_ID=ua/Privacy _full &locale.x=en_US

**Links to Other Websites.**

GaggleAMP.com and messages posted in any Gaggle may contain links or references to other websites. GaggleAMP.com cannot control and cannot be held responsible for the content that appears on those sites, and is not an endorsement, authorization, or representation of our affiliation with that third party. Furthermore, GaggleAMP is not responsible for the privacy policies of any third party site or for how they treat information about their users. These third party sites may place their own cookies on your computer, collect data, or solicit personal information. You may be consenting to those websites through use of ours. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements and terms of service for each of the other websites you visit.

**Our Policy Towards Children.**

The Site is not directed to persons under 18. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personally identifiable information without their consent, he or she should contact us at privacy@gaggleamp.com. We will take actions to promptly remove such data. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 18. If we become aware that a child under 18 has provided us with personally identifiable Information, we will delete such information from our files.
